getmyuni.com 2015-06-15

# GetMyUni: Privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**

We respect the privacy of visitors to the websites owned by GETMYUNI SAS (hereafter "the Website") and take care that the personal data which you provide us is handled in a confidential manner. The processing of the personal data happens in accordance with the demands of the French law (Loi n° 2004-575 du 21 juin 2004 pour la confiance dans l'économie numérique et la Loi "Informatique et libertés" du 6 janvier 1978 modifiée en 2004).

**Data processing**

Your personal data will be processed for the entering into agreements and the performance thereof to the point of commercial services and the managing of the business relations which emerge from them, including the performance of activities aimed at the expansion of our client database.

If you fill out a contact or registration form on the Website, or send us an e-mail, the data provided by you will be stored for as long as the nature of the form or the contents of your e-mail demand with regards to the handling and answering thereof.

**Click-behaviour and Visit Data**

General visitor data is registered on the website. This can notably include the IP-address of your computer, the possible username, the moment of retrieval and data sent by the browser of the visitor. This data is registered and used for statistical analyses of visit data and click-behaviour on the Website. Additionally this data is used for optimization of the Website. We try to keep this data as anonymous as we can.

**Google Analytics**

We make use of Google Analytics to keep track of how visitors use the Website and how effective our AdWords-advertisements are on Google´s search results. The acquired data is, including the address of your computer (IP-address), transferred to and by Google to be stored in servers in the United States. Please read Google´s privacy policy for more data in addition to Google Analytics specific privacy policy.

Google uses this data to keep track of how the Website is used, to report on the use of the Website to us and to be able to inform its advertisers about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google can share this data with third parties when they are required to do so by Law, or to the extent that third parties process this data for Google. We have no influence on how Google performs its business practices. We have not granted permission to Google to use the acquired data for any other services provided by Google.

**Social media**

Incorporated in the Website are buttons to promote or share web-pages on the social networks Facebook and Twitter, as well as the AddThis toolbar to promote or share web-pages on other social networks, blogs and through email. These buttons are realized by code supplied by AddThis, Facebook and Twitter and not by Getmyuni. This code places a cookie.

Please read the privacy statements of AddThis, Facebook and Twitter (which are changed on a regular basis) to see what they do with the personal data which is acquired and processed by this code.

**User account**

You can create an account in order to customize their experience. As registered user you can for instance save your favourite schools, programmes or search queries, and more easily contact the other users and the universities of your interest. 

**E-mail services**

You can create an account in order to customize their experience. As registered user you can for instance save your favourite schools, programmes or search queries, and more easily contact the other users and the universities of your interest.

**Cookies**

We make use of cookies in the offering and performance of our electronic services. A cookie is a simple small file which is sent along with the web-pages of the Website and is saved on your hard-drive by your browser. We use cookies to save your options and preferences. You can disable these cookies through your browser.

Cookies from the American company Google are placed through the Website as part of the "Analytics"-service. We use this service to keep track of and acquire data on how visitors use the Website. Google can share data when required to do so by law, or to the extent that third parties process this data for Google. We have no influence on how Google performs its business practices.

**Insight, correction and removal**

When you have a relation with Getmyuni, you have after written request the option to view your personal data. In case the data provided by us contains errors, you can make a written request to have the data corrected or to have it removed. In addition you can inform us in writing that you do not desire to be approached with data on our products and services by reporting this to the following address:

GETMYUNI SAS, 48 rue de Patay, 75013 PARIS, FRANCE

**Change to the privacy statement**

We retain the right to alter or otherwise make changes to this privacy statement. Changes will be announced on the Website.
